Guide to the Edward W. Kelley, Jr. Federal Reserve papers, 1986-2010 MS 492
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Edward W. Kelley, Jr. Federal Reserve papers
1986-2010
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Kelley, Edward Watson
MS 492
8.5 Linear Feet (17 boxes)
Meeting notes, agendas, transcripts and reports mainly related to E.W. Kelley's work on Federal Open Market Committee as Governor for the Federal Reserve's Board of Governors.
Biographical / Historical
Edward W. Kelley, Jr. was president of Kelley Industries, a Houston-based holding company with businesses in manufacturing and distribution. He then served as chairman of the board of Investment Advisors, also in Houston. In 1987, his valuable perspective as a business executive was called upon when he began a term of service as a governor on the Federal Reserve board. He was instrumental in preparing the Federal Reseve system for Y2K, to make sure the Federal computer sytems would keep running as the year 1999 turned over into 2000. These preparations helped the same system keep running effortlessly after the 2001 terrorist attacks. Kelley served on the Federal Reserve board until 2001, when he retired. He was honored in 2005 by having the new Federal Reserve branch bank building in Houston named after him, and praised by then Federal Reseve Chairman Alan Greenspan in a speech at the building's dedication.
Scope and Contents
Meeting notes, agendas, transcripts and reports mainly related to E.W. Kelley's work on Federal Open Market Committee as Governor for the Federal Reserve's Board of Governors.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was donated by Edward W. Kelley, Jr., 2002-2008, and 2013.
Index Terms
Subjects
Federal Reserve banks; Business
Document Types
oral histories (document genres); photographs; reports; letters (correspondence); minutes (administrative records)
- Series I: Business Files, 75052
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence, notes, publications filed by Kelley in chronological order by year.
  - Dec. 1986-1990, 75053 (Box 1)
    - Notes and correspondence re: candidacy, 1986-1987; 78965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Congratulatory notes and telegrams, 1987; 78966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Cards and letters; folder 1 of 2, 1987; 78967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Cards and letters; folder 2 of 2, 1987; 78968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Congressional Records, May 1987; 78969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper clippings re: Fed position, 1987; 78970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Guest lists and invitations for going away parties, May 30-June 16, 1987; 78971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Swearing-in programs and activities, June 17-20, 1987; 78972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Swearing-in Ceremony, FRB Board Room (3 audio cassettes), June 18, 1987; 78973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - E.W. Kelley, Jr.'s Federal Diary (2 audio cassettes), 1987; 78974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - News articles re: the economy and stock market crash, 1987; 78975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - "A Short History of the Creation of the Federal Reserve System" booklet, 78976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - St. John's School newsletter, October 1987; 78977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Photographs of Board of Governors, 1988; 78978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - News clips and conference programs, 1988; 78979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - The Executives' Club of Chicago directory, 1988-1989; 78980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - The Oregonian Business Forecast, 1988-1989; 78981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - The American Bicentennial Presidential Inaugural, 1989; 78982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - News clips and reports, 1989; 78983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1989; 78984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Oath of Office papers and photos, 1990; 78985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Congressional Records, 1990; 78986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 1990-1995, 75054 (Box 2)
    - News clips and reports, 1990; 78987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and programs, 1990; 78988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Meeting at Banco Central del Uruguay, 1990; 78989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Congressional records, 1991; 78990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - News clips and reports, 1991; 78991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and programs, 1991; 78992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Speech at Houston Baptist University (programs, photo, 1 audio cassette), 1991; 78993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, 1991; 78994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - "Annual Oversight Hearing on the Budget of the Federal Reserve System, Governors Angell and Kelley" (1 video cassette), July 18, 1991; 78995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - News clips and reports, 1992; 78996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1992; 78997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Programs, 1992; 78998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Photographs, 1992; 78999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Reuniones de Gobernadores de Bancos Centrales, 1992; 79000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Congressional Records (The Federal Reserve Accountability Act of 1993), 79001 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - News clips and reports, 1993; 79002 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1993; 79003 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Programs, 1993; 79004 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Photographs, 1993; 79005 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Congressional Records (Design of the Currency), 1994; 79006 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - News clips and reports, 1994; 79007 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1994; 79008 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Programs, 1994; 79009 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Photographs, 1994; 79010 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Symposium Proceedings handbook, 1994; 79011 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Congressional Records (The $1 Coin), 1995; 79012 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - News clips and reports, 1995; 79013 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 1995-1999, 75055 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence, 1995; 79014 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Programs, 1995; 79015 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Photographs, 1995; 79016 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - News clips and reports, 1996; 79017 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and photos of Kelley, 1996; 79018 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Programs, 1996; 79019 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Congressional Records, 1996-1998; 79020 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - News clips and reports, 1997; 79021 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1997; 79022 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Programs, 1997; 79023 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Photographs of Kelley and Board of Governors, 79024 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Congressional Records, 1998; 79025 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - News clips and reports, 1998; 79026 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1998; 79027 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Programs, 1998; 79028 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Photographs of Kelley and Federal Reserve Board, 1998; 79029 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Federal Reserve System Commemorative Stamp, 1998; 79030 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - E.W. Kelley, Jr.'s official passports, 1987-1998; 79031 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Congressional Records, 1999; 79032 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Newsclips and reports, 1999; 79033 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1999; 79034 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Programs, 1999; 79035 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Photographs of Kelley, Jr., 1999; 79036 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Departure from Federal Reserve, 2000-2001, 75056 (Box 4)
    - Y2K Event Schedule, CD Album, Timer and Audio cassette, 79037 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - News clips and reports, 2000-2001; 79038 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Post-heart attack "get well" cards, 2000; 79039 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 2000-2001; 79040 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Programs, 2000; 79041 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, 2000-2001; 79042 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Resignation and Departure, 2001; 79043 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Members of the Board of Governors bios and photos, 79044 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - News about and transcripts of remarks by E.W. Kelley, Jr., sent to Mrs. Kelley (mother), 1987-1996; 79045 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Nametags from various events attended by Kelley (folder 1 of 2), 79046 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Nametags from various events attended by Kelley (folder 2 of 2), 79047 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Y2K files, 1999-2000, 75058 (Box 4-5)
    - Y2K Speeches and Testimonies, 79048 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Century date change - early publications, 79049 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Year 2000 Conversion, 79050 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Y2K Testimony, Sept. 17, 1998; 79051 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Year 2000 testimony, April 29, 1998; 79052 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Year 2000 testimony, House Banking Committee, Nov. 4, 1997; 79053 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Year 2000 testimony, July 30, 1997; 79054 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Y2K Communications, 1999; 79055 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Year 2000 Overview: A presentation to the Board of Governonrs, April 14, 1999; 79056 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The Journey to Y2K: Final Report of the President's Council on Year 2000 Conversion, March 29, 2000; 79057 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Cosmos Club Speech, March 30, 2000; 79058 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Y2K Celebration, 79059 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Meeting with Retailer Groups - BD ROOM, April 13, 1999; 79060 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - CDC Contingency Planning, 79061 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - "CDC - Contingency and Event Planning", 79062 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Board Event Management Plan, 79064 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - President's Council on Y2K Conversion (folder 1 of 2), 79065 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - President's Council on Y2K Conversion (folder 2 of 2), 79066 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Blair House Y2K Seminar with Cabinet, Saturday, 9/18/99; 79067 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - CDC Q & A, 79068 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - CDC International Preparations, 79069 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Y2K Public Information (folder 1 of 2), 79070 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Y2K Public Information (folder 2 of 2), 79071 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Public Information, 79072 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Y2K Run-up, 79073 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Y2K Currency Preparation, 79074 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Y2K Currency, 79075 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Speeches by Kelley, 75062 (Box 5-6)
    - Remarks: Special Occasions, 79076 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Remarks: FRS Groups (folder 1 of 2), 79077 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Remarks: FRS Groups (folder 2 of 2), 79078 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Remarks: Economics & Forecasts (folder 1 of 3), 79079 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Remarks: Economics & Forecasts (folder 2 of 3), 79080 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Remarks: Economics & Forecasts (folder 3 of 3), 79081 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Remarks: General Topics (folder 1 of 4), 79082 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Remarks: General Topics (folder 2 of 4), 79083 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Remarks: General Topics (folder 3 of 4), 79084 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Remarks: General Topics (folder 4 of 4), 79085 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Speeches & Testimonies (folder 1 of 3), 79086 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Speeches & Testimonies (folder 2 of 3), 79087 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Speeches & Testimonies (folder 3 of 3), 79088 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Series II: Federal Open Market Committee meeting transcripts, agendas and notes, 1987-1996, 75059
  - 1987-1989, 75060 (Box 6)
    - Transcripts of Federal Open Market Committee, 1987; 79090 (Box 6, Folder -)
    - FOMC (folder 1 of 2), 1987; 79089 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - FOMC (folder 2 of 2), 1987; 79091 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - FOMC, December 1987; 79092 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Transcripts of Federal Open Market Committee, 1988; 79093 (Box 6, Folder -)
    - FOMC, February 1988; 79094 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - FOMC, March 1988; 79095 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - FOMC, May 1988; 79096 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - FOMC, June 1988; 79097 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - FOMC, August 1988; 79098 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - FOMC, September 1988; 79099 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - FOMC, October 1988; 79100 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - FOMC, November 1988; 79101 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - FOMC, December 1988; 79102 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1989-1990, 75061 (Box 7)
    - Transcripts of Federal Open Market Committee, 1989; 79103 (Box 7, Folder -)
    - FOMC, February 1989; 79104 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - FOMC, March 1989; 79105 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - FOMC, May 1989; 79106 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - FOMC, June 1989; 79107 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - FOMC, July 1989; 79108 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - FOMC, August 1989; 79109 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - FOMC, September 1989; 79110 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - FOMC, October 1989; 79111 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - FOMC, November 1989; 79112 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - FOMC, December 1989; 79113 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Transcripts of Federal Open Market Committee, 1990; 79114 (Box 7, Folder -)
    - FOMC, January 1990; 79115 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - FOMC, February 1990; 79116 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - FOMC, March 1990; 79117 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - FOMC, May 1990; 79118 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - FOMC, June 1990; 79119 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - FOMC, July 1990; 79120 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - FOMC, August 1990; 79121 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - FOMC, September 1990; 79122 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - FOMC, November 1990; 79123 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - FOMC, December 1990; 79124 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 1991-1993, 75063 (Box 8)
    - Transcripts of Federal Open Market Committee, 1991; 79125 (Box 8, Folder -)
    - FOMC, January 1991; 79126 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - FOMC, February 1991; 79127 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - FOMC, March 1991; 79128 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - FOMC, May 1991; 79129 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - FOMC, June 1991; 79130 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - FOMC, July 1991; 79131 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - FOMC, August 1991; 79132 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - FOMC, October 1991; 79133 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - FOMC, November 1991; 79134 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - FOMC, December 1991; 79135 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Transcripts of Federal Open Market Committee, 1992; 79136 (Box 8, Folder -)
    - FOMC, January 1992; 79137 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - FOMC, February 1992; 79138 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - FOMC, March 1992; 79139 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - FOMC, May 1992; 79140 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - FOMC, June 1992; 79141 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - FOMC, August 1992; 79142 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - FOMC, September 1992; 79143 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - FOMC, October 1992; 79144 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - FOMC, November 1992; 79145 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - FOMC, December 1992; 79146 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Transcripts of Federal Open Market Committee (folder 1 of 2), 1993; 79147 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Transcripts of Federal Open Market Committee (folder 2 of 2), 1993; 79148 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - FOMC, January 1993; 79149 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - FOMC, February 1993; 79150 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - 1993-1996, 75064
    - FOMC, March 1993; 79151 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - FOMC, May 1993; 79152
    - FOMC, June 1993; 79153
    - FOMC, July 1993; 79154
    - FOMC, August 1993; 79155
    - FOMC, September 1993; 79156
    - FOMC, November 1993; 79157
    - FOMC, December 1993; 79158
    - Transcripts of Federal Open Market Committee (folder 1 of 2), 1994; 79159
    - Transcripts of Federal Open Market Committee (folder 2 of 2), 1994; 79160
    - FOMC, January 1994; 79161
    - FOMC, February 1994; 79162
    - FOMC, March 1994; 79163
    - FOMC, May 1994; 79164
    - FOMC, June 1994; 79165
    - FOMC, July 1994; 79166
    - FOMC, August 1994; 79167
    - FOMC, September 1994; 79168
    - FOMC, November 1994; 79169
    - FOMC, December 1994; 79170
    - Transcripts of Federal Open Market Committee (folder 1 of 2), 1995; 79171
    - Transcripts of Federal Open Market Committee (folder 2 of 2), 1995; 79172
    - FOMC, January 1995; 79173
    - FOMC, March 1995; 79174
    - FOMC, May 1995; 79175
    - FOMC, July 1995; 79176
    - FOMC, August 1995; 79177
    - FOMC, September 1995; 79178
    - FOMC, November 1995; 79179
    - FOMC, December 1995; 79180
    - FOMC, January 1996; 79181
    - FOMC, March 1996; 79182
    - FOMC, May 1996; 79183
  - 1996-2001, 75065 (Box 10)
    - FOMC, July 1996; 79184 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - FOMC, August 1996; 79185 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - FOMC, September 1996; 79186 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - FOMC, November 1996; 79187 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - FOMC, December 1996; 79188 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - FOMC, January 1997; 79189 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - FOMC, March 1997; 79190 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - FOMC, May 1997; 79191 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - FOMC, July 1997; 79192 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - FOMC, August 1997; 79193 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - FOMC, September 1997; 79194 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - FOMC, November 1997; 79195 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - FOMC, June 1998; 79196 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - FOMC, August 1998; 79197 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - FOMC, September 1998; 79198 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - FOMC, November 1998; 79199 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - FOMC, December 1998; 79200 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - FOMC, January 1999; 79201 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - FOMC, February 1999; 79202 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - FOMC, March 1999; 79203 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - FOMC, May 1999; 79204 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - FOMC, June 1999; 79205 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - FOMC, August 1999; 79206 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - FOMC, October 1999; 79207 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - FOMC, November 1999; 79208 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - FOMC, December 1999; 79209 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - FOMC, February 2000; 79210 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - FOMC, March 2000; 79211 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - FOMC, May 2000; 79212 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - FOMC, June 2000; 79213 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - FOMC, August 2000; 79214 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - FOMC, October 2000; 79215 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - FOMC, November 2000; 79216 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - FOMC, December 2000; 79217 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - FOMC, January 2001; 79218 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - FOMC, March 2001; 79219 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - FOMC, May 2001; 79220 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - FOMC, June 2001; 79221 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - FOMC, August 2001; 79222 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - FOMC, September 2001; 79223 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - FOMC, October 2001; 79224 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - FOMC, November 2001; 79225 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - FOMC Press releases, 1987-1996; 75066 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Series III: FOMC "Current Economic & Financial Conditions" & "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, 1987-2001, 75067
  - 1987-1989, 75068 (Box 11)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, May-August, 1987; 79226 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, September-December, 1987; 79227 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, May-December 1987; 79228 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, February-May, 1988; 79229 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, June-September, 1988; 79230 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, October-December, 1988; 79231 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, February-December, 1988; 79232 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, February-May, 1989; 79233 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, June-September, 1989; 79234 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, November-December, 1989; 79235 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, February-December, 1989; 79236 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 1990-1992, 75069 (Box 12)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, January-March, 1990; 79237 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, May-August, 1990; 79238 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, September-November, 1990; 79239 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, November-December, 1990; 79240 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, February-June, 1990; 79241 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, August-December, 1990; 79242 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, January-March, 1991; 79243 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, May-June, 1991; 79244 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, August-September, 1991; 79245 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, October-December, 1991; 79246 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, February-June, 1991; 79247 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, August-December, 1991; 79248 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, January-March, 1992; 79249 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, May-June, 1992; 79250 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, August-September, 1992; 79251 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, November-December, 1992; 79252 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, January-June, 1992; 79253 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, August-December, 1992; 79254 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - 1993-1995, 75070 (Box 13)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, January-March, 1993; 79255 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, May-June, 1993; 79256 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, August-September, 1993; 79257 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, November-December, 1993; 79258 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, January-July, 1993; 79259 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, August-December, 1993; 79260 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, January-March, 1994; 79261 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, May-June, 1994; 79262 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, August-September, 1994; 79263 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, November-December, 1994; 79264 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, January-June, 1994; 79265 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, August-December, 1994; 79266 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, January-March, 1995; 79267 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, May-June, 1995; 79268 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, August-September, 1995; 79269 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, November-December, 1995; 79270 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, January-May, 1995; 79271 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, June-December, 1995; 79272 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - 1996-1998, 75071 (Box 14)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, January-March, 1996; 79273 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, May-June, 1996; 79274 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, August-September, 1996; 79275 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, November-December, 1996; 79276 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, January-June, 1996; 79277 (Box 14, Folder 5)